

Front-end Developer stepanosadchii103@gmail.com +382 68 756284 Bar, Montenegro

Date / Place of birth 24.10.1999 / Barnaul

Nationality Russian

Stepan Osadchii

Profile

Front-end React developer with 1.5+ year of commercial experience. I work with technologies such as JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Mobs, and also have a little experience in developing a backend on Node.Js using technologies such as NestJS, Express, TypeORM, PostgresSQL, Redis. He participated in projects from large customers, developed from scratch a universal configurator for a large online store, a platform for creating microcontroller firmware, a script for analyzing user actions and displaying recommendations for him.

Employment History

Fornt-end developeratFreematiq (full time), Barnaul

07/2021-Present

I was engaged in the development of React applications from scratch, as well as participated in other projects of the company to refine the current functionality. I actively used TypeScript, React, MobX in my work.

- Optimized React application and reduced loading time by 560%, for this I transferred the project to the NextJS library.
- Refactor outdated projects in SPA applications using React, ReactRouter, StyledComponents and MobX
- Designed REST API with diverse data validation, documenting using Swagger editor and OpenAPI specification, for this task I used NestJS and TypeOrm

Back-end developeratFreematiq (internship), Barnaul

05/2021-07/2021

As part of the internship, I made a universal assembly for the admin panel from scratch, then improved the project by rewriting it to NestJS.

In the process, I actively worked with such technologies and frameworks as: Express, Net Js, Type Rm, Sequelize, Postgresql. I also got a little acquainted with unit tests on Jest.

Links

<u>Telegram</u> LinkedIn

Skills

React
TypeScript
JavaScript
HTML
CSS
SCSS
BEM
WebPack
Node.js
Express
NestJs
TypeOrm
Postgres

Docker

Git

Languages

Russian	Native speaker
English	B1
Polish	A2

Education

Bachelor, Altai State Technical University, Barnaul

08/2021—Present